I don't want nobody to get killed
I come and get you, I'm always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame, we're always wet
Oh, I don't take all of the blame, you always do
There will always be something you cannot control
We will overcome, your salvation has begun
No sun, no light, such a mess, I won't go
Don't kill your walls, you make me realize who I need
I'll be there, hold on, the change is somehow
So where are you now?
I'll reach you, my top, the shadows of the earth
Illusions apart
The golden end is too wrong, but I know it is a pain
That makes us a human after all
Toin and save you for the control
About your precious worth
This scar may respond to your call
This is it
To be honest, you guys might be able to fend off the vampires on your own
Since you have the Black Demon series
But that's dangerous
So I think it'd be best for us to stick together
Be careful
And whatever you do, don't break from a...
Yeah, yeah, I won't
At least you recognize I could do it alone
That's enough for me
All right, team
Let's move out
The little girl we rescued said that there are seven vampires down here
With any luck, they're sleeping right now and we can take them by surprise
Whatever the case, we do this by the book
It's important that we stay in formation and watch each other's backs
Don't get separated
And don't act alone
What is this?
They're dressed like livestock
Let's keep moving
We're going straight to B3
That's the floor the vampire should be on
If no one's guarding them
Then why don't the captives escape?
Because it's crawling with monsters outside
The vampires promise to protect them is the lesser of two evils
And in return they offer up their blood?
Those bloodsuckers won't get another drop from them
That's as though they will be locked in
They sheerly
It's元imes
That's why it's turned here
mateix
That's what's coming
Bucking up
salted
flow
Form up! Prepare to attack!
Drop!
Don't let him call for backup!
Ah!
Livestock! You pay for this!
How does it feel to be killed by your food, you bastard?
Burn in hell!
One down.
Damn you.
Yuichiro!
How many times have I told you not to jump ahead and act on your own?
I followed your rules.
I assessed the enemy and didn't draw until you said to.
You need to stop complaining and give me some credit.
Not fast enough.
I've waited four years to do this.
Now you're gonna pay.
You imbecile.
Just because you blocked me one of the...
Whoa.
Where's this power coming from?
That was amazing!
I figured he had to be good since the lieutenant colonel has taken such an interest in his training.
But I didn't know he was this strong.
Yeah, you wasted that BAMP.
You're almost as good as I am, chump.
Almost?
Let's test that.
Just you and me, one-on-one.
You couldn't handle it.
If we were to fight, you'd be dead before you could even get your sword out.
Bring it on, four-eyes.
Call me that one more time.
I dare you.
Four-eyes.
You're asking for punk.
They're the lieutenant colonel's favorites.
A couple of troublemakers who are bad at teamwork.
I bet he put you on this squad so you can whip the boys into shape and make them better soldiers.
That's enough messing around.
We've still got five more targets left.
They've come to us.
Get ready.
Ah!
Mitsuba!
Eight of them.
You're not supposed to be here.
Our intelligence was solid.
Your intelligence?
Ha ha!
And just where do you think that information came from?
Thanks for saving me.
I'll tell you.
You used her!
An innocent little girl!
Ha ha!
Human beings are so disgusting.
Threatened to drain the blood from the people they care about most, and they'll do anything you ask of them.
Don't attack!
I'm as good as dead now!
Retreat!
Why do I keep having to repeat myself?
There's no way I'm ever leaving a comrade behind.
I'm sorry, but I have to disobey!
You...
Got to check on...
It's going to get you!
!
Go!
No!
Stop it!
No! Stop it!
Sink yourself!
We're still... I can't...
Damn livestock.
He saved her!
What was it you said about humans being disgusting?
That we're scum who'll turn on one another if you threaten our friends and family?
That we don't have a sense of pride?
I guess you know us pretty well.
What you said is true.
Humans will do anything for the people we care about.
We'll push ourselves to the brink, make contracts with demons, and become devils ourselves.
You might think that's repulsive.
But I would call it honorable.
The disgusting one is you!
Wow! You really know how to rile them up.
Right. Let's do this.
We can take these guys.
Absolutely.
From what I can tell, all of them are armed with second-class weapons.
But there are still a few more of them than us.
We were outnumbered from the start.
What do you say?
Strike hard.
Don't let a single one of them escape.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Thank you.
You're safe!
Sir, please forgive me.
They...
I didn't...
Sorry!
You're trying to protect the people you care about.
I get that.
I put you in danger.
You were doing what you thought was right.
No need to apologize.
After being rescued from a dangerous situation, the girl watches her knight in shining armor.
Passion fills the air.
These two are destined to fall in love.
Not gonna happen.
Don't be ridiculous.
Do you know what Yuu's story is?
Hmm?
No.
what happened to you is it true did you leave your friends behind when they were attacked
that's none of your damn business don't poke around in my past wait
you were right to i know that this probably doesn't mean anything coming from me
but still i don't think you did anything wrong i'm glad you survived i left my family behind
to save my own skin even though they were dying i should have stayed with them until the end
i can't change what happened that's why i will never
just forget it you i've said everything i
earlier he had me i wanna say
oh wait you wanna say what just that you almost got us all killed today you idiot
that's what this is about hey are you two lovebirds done flirting yet ready to go
huh you shut up
oh you've got to be kidding me you really know how to hotwire a car
yeah well this is perfect we finally found something you're good at would you shut up
but seriously the only time i've ridden in a car was when i was a little kid
i almost forgot about them there weren't any in the vampire city plus gas is so rare nowadays that
you hardly ever see them around shibuya
hell yeah you did it let's ride hey kamizuki uh when's it gonna be my turn to drive this thing
never you've got no experience behind the wheel well not technically but i am quick learner
just don't touch anything for now i'll give you an intro lesson or something later
you mean you can hotwire and drive a car i guess you are cool
you're like the annoying little brother i never wanted
these actually aren't that bad i got it started thanks to any of you impressive
so where'd you learn how to do that you do know that it's a crime to steal a car right
can you please whatever let's just get on the road
crap that wasn't right then it must be this way
what the fuck do you think you're
i'm gonna kill you
hey hop in i think i've got this driving thing figured out
so dead don't you ever try that again
are those two ever gonna stop fighting
probably not well it looks as if my expert driving skills are required once again
wait you're gonna try
get in next stop shinjuku
you can't even see over the stairs
you know why you're way too short
you think so
you know we probably shouldn't make fun of shinoa's height anymore
i actually agree with you for once
what's that maybe a four horsemen of john
should we go kill it no if we kill one then more will just show up
let's head to shinjuku and see if we can lose them
not good
that banging sound we're headed straight forward
all right everyone stay on alert we have no idea who or what might be waiting for us here
shinjuku is just ahead we should be able to see the defensive barrier soon
we're at his people
what the
No, don't slow down! Hit him! That guy's a noble!
I need this! My sword. Gain power from my blood.
No way!
Joichi!
That was something. He's strong.
Listen up! Stay in formation. He is wielding a first-class weapon. No one attacks him alone.
I'm going to kill you.
Hey, you're pretty good for a human. Who are you exactly?
You guys okay?
Chinoa? Fine. Yuichiro and Kamizuki should take points since they're the strongest one-on-one fighters. The rest of us will cover them and tag in if things start to look rough. We can't underestimate this guy's abilities.
This is bad. Things just took a turn for the worse.
What now? Do we retreat?
Getting out of here would be the best idea, but I doubt these three will let us do that. So we fight in full power. We let the demons almost completely possess us. But that still might not be enough.
Yes. We might not survive. But we are soldiers. We knew that from the start.
Okay, fine. If that's how it's going to be, just know that I'm not going to let any of you die. That's the whole reason I fought for so much power. Right, Ashramaru?
Um, Lord Crowley? What are you doing wasting your time with these humans? The seventh progenitor is waiting for you at the front line.
Hmm? Ferret wants to see me. I probably shouldn't keep him waiting. Pity. Things were just starting to get interesting here.
Very well. I suppose this can wait until later. I'll let all of you go for today. But next time we meet, I'm draining every last drop of your blood.
What?
So long for now, my cute little blood bag.
We're okay. We don't have to fight.
That arrogant jerk. What a bastard. Treating us as if we were his playthings.
Pull yourself together. We need to get out of here before they start having second thoughts. Let's meet up with the Shinjuku units.
Damn it! This is all wrong. I've got a cursed gear. I'm supposed to be as strong as he is.
Well, since you've got the Black Demon series, you could always learn some curses. That'd help get you closer to his power level.
Then why haven't you taught me any?
Well, I could. But what good is it if you're the only one who can defeat a powerful vampire?
I'd probably be killed while you fought.
Yoichi.
Mitsuba.
They'd just end up dying, too.
That's why we have to work together.
All of us have to keep training so that we fight as a unit of equals.
We're improving. I was happy to hear you ask about retreating. And there's something else I have to say.
Thank you for saving my life earlier, Yu. It's like Lieutenant Colonel Gurren said. You care about your friends.
Huh? Oh, it was nothing.
You know, I'm kind of ready to go back to Shibuya.
I hear you. But right now it's not an option. If Shinjuku falls, then Shibuya's next.
Your sister's there. Remember that when we fight.
Let's get moving.
We won't lose Shinjuku.
Right.
Let's get moving.
I need your blood, your real love tonight, our God's great light.
I need your blood, your spirit, your love tonight, our God's great light.
Yon gao shi ga kiunade toNaoたが
Li gonna be talking about the storm
fire attack.